Finding aid for Lon G. Nungesser Hope for Humanity Papers, 1970-1989
University of Michigan Library (Special Collections Research Center)
- Photo Albums
  - Photo Album One: The Early Years with Bill
    - Yes, the garden was bare, but oh what fun we had planning the next crop! (Volume 1, Page 65)
    - Spring garden preparation (Volume 1, Page 66)
    - Bill, 1984 (Volume 1, Page 67)
    - Lon (oops, the love handles are showing!) (Volume 1, Page 67)
    - The rocking chair that Lon built for Bill (Volume 1, Page 68)
    - Peaceful kitties (Volume 1, Page 69)
    - Fall, 1985 garden (Volume 1, Page 70)
    - Spring, 1986 garden (Volume 1, Page 71)
    - - the star was designed to be geometrically exact Spring, 1986 (Volume 1, Page 72)
    - Lon fixing oatmeal cookies (Volume 1, Page 72)
    - The beginnings of a chicken coop (Volume 1, Page 73)
    - Bill trying to keep the cats out of his way while he built the chicken coop (Volume 1, Page 73)
    - Bill, the carpenter (Volume 1, Page 74)
    - Bill, the beer drinking carpenter (Volume 1, Page 74)
    - Capping off the coop (Volume 1, Page 75)
    - I just had to start with baby chicks (Volume 1, Page 76)
      (Top 4)
    - The garden is ready to plant, Spring of 1986 (Volume 1, Page 76)
    - Bill holding "Clarence" (Volume 1, Page 77)
    - Lon after tending the lettuce bed (Volume 1, Page 77)
    - The coop is done! (Volume 1, Page 78)
    - Lon at his tulip bed, holding "Clarence" (Volume 1, Page 78)
    - Our Rhode Island Red pullets and a hybrid Leghorn (Clarence) (Volume 1, Page 79)
    - The house we lived in when Lon was diagnosed and planted the gardens (Volume 1, Page 79)
    - Lon with Dr. Cherrie Boyer, a graduate school mate (Volume 1, Page 80)
    - The tulip bed in Spring (Volume 1, Page 80)
    - Second crop of strawberries (Volume 1, Page 81)
    - My chickletts (Volume 1, Page 82)
      (All)
    - Pre-pubescent chicks (Volume 1, Page 83)
    - The star after Tulip season (Volume 1, Page 84)
    - When I foolishly followed a city-dweller's advice and covered the garden with straw to prevent weeds; How the weeds grew under that straw! (Volume 1, Page 85)
    - Bill's renovated garage turned Summer House (Volume 1, Page 86)
    - And he juggles, too! (Volume 1, Page 87)
    - California poppies galore (Volume 1, Page 88)
    - Adolescent chicks (Volume 1, Page 88)
    - All I asked for was a smile...but this will do! (Volume 1, Page 89)
    - A summer lunch (Volume 1, Page 90)
    - 1986 Summer garden: Okra, squash, corn and beans (Volume 1, Page 91)
    - Lon: The irrepressible conflict resolver. Typical mediation with both sides not wanting to be there! (Volume 1, Page 92)
    - My how our garden grew! (Volume 1, Page 93)
    - Raising chickens has been fun, but what do you do with a dozen eggs a day! (Volume 1, Page 94)
    - Can you find the cantaloupes in this photo? (Volume 1, Page 95)
    - At last a photo of the moss rose without a cat! (Volume 1, Page 96)
    - Erica, the hen that laid multi-colored eggs (Volume 1, Page 97)
    - Lon playing among the Hollyhocks (Volume 1, Page 98)
    - Lon letting the chickens roam the garden with Jasmine on guard (Volume 1, Page 99)
    - Mid-summer Marigolds (Volume 1, Page 100)
  - Photo Album Two: More Cherished Moments with Bill
    - The 8' tall Sunflowers I grew from tiny seeds (Volume 2, Page 1)
    - 1985 Spice bed (Volume 2, Page 2)
    - Summer, `85 flower bed (Volume 2, Page 3)
    - Summer '85 spice bed: Basil, sage, aloe vera, peppermint, scallions & parsley (Volume 2, Page 4)
    - Ruby the Rhode Island Red hen. She was my pet, and often produced double-yolked eggs. (Volume 2, Page 4)
    - The climbing gourdes produced bushels of Fall color. (Volume 2, Page 5)
    - An onion goes to seed, and Hollyhocks are mixed with Sunflowers for a colorful background (Volume 2, Page 6)
    - Summer squash & fflowers at their peak of blooming, 1985 (Volume 2, Page 7)
    - Summer `85 Moss Rose, Marigolds and Hollyhocks (Volume 2, Page 8)
    - Petunias and Pansies in full bloom at the base of a pear tree. (Volume 2, Page 9)
    - The chicken flock (Volume 2, Page 10 & 11)
    - A new hybrid flock of young pullets, a cross between Rhode Island Reds & Leghorns (Volume 2, Page 12)
    - Jasper, the friendly rooster with no concept of time - he would crow at all hours so we ate him! (Volume 2, Page 13)
    - Jasper on his roost (Volume 2, Page 14)
    - Vines, vines everywhere! (Volume 2, Page 14)
    - The third summer we stringed all vines on trellis' or ropes - what a maze! (Volume 2, Page 15)
    - Jasper at his best (Volume 2, Page 16)
    - Try finding your way in this garden jungle! (Volume 2, Page 16)
    - My "Star Flower Bed" with Petunias, Marigolds, Pansies, Moss Rose, California Poppies, Sweet William, Carnations and Allisum. (Volume 2, Page 17)
    - Flower beds, 1986 (Volume 2, Page 18)
    - Flower bed & Chicken house, 1985 (Volume 2, Page 19)
    - Flower bed & Chicken house, 1986 (Volume 2, Page 20)
    - The hens invading Jasper's space (Volume 2, Page 20)
    - Erica on the attack of a second crop of chicks walking in her food (Volume 2, Page 21)
    - Sitting among the flowers was one of my most peaceful activities (Volume 2, Page 21)
    - The pole beans are taking over! (Volume 2, Page 22)
    - My prize gladiolus (Volume 2, Page 23)
    - Weeds beneath the straw (Volume 2, Page 24)
    - Chard going to seed (Volume 2, Page 24)
    - The 1986 garden on the grow (Volume 2, Page 25)
    - The garage turned in to a summer house (Volume 2, Page 25)
    - More weeds florishing beneath the straw (Volume 2, Page 26)
    - The Star Flower Bed in transition (Volume 2, Page 27)
    - Chicks in the shade (Volume 2, Page 28)
    - Onions & chives at their peak of production (Volume 2, Page 28)
    - Gourds climbing over a walk-way beside the garage/summer house (Volume 2, Page 29)
    - More gourds (Volume 2, Page 30)
    - And more gourds! (Volume 2, Page 31)
    - Onions & sage in bloom; twine awaits the climbing squash (Volume 2, Page 32)
    - July, 1986 flower bed (Volume 2, Page 33)
    - Gourds on the climb (Volume 2, Page 34)
    - Petunias & sweet william (Volume 2, Page 34)
    - An apricot retrieved from near-death by Bill's expert landscaping skills and knowledge of vitamin therapy (Volume 2, Page 35)
    - An 8' sunflower (Volume 2, Page 36)
    - Late summer, `86 (Volume 2, Page 37)
    - Summer crop fades and goes to seed (Volume 2, Page 38)
    - Towering sunflowers line the garden's outer edge (Volume 2, Page 39)
    - Lon in 1986 garden (Volume 2, Page 40)
    - A well-tanned Bill stands tall beside a towering sunflower (Volume 2, Page 41)
    - A fine crop of corn (Volume 2, Page 42)
    - Eggplant, pole beans and squash (Volume 2, Page 42)
    - Sage, rosemary, parsley, peppermint and basil (Volume 2, Page 43)
    - Green pole beans climbing early sweet corn with snow peas in front (Volume 2, Page 43)
    - Winter, 1986 garden (Volume 2, Page 44)
    - Pole beans mixed with snow peas (Volume 2, Page 44)
    - Beans climbing behind okra and snow peas (Volume 2, Page 45)
    - Bill holding Ruby - which of these characters is most apprehensive? (Volume 2, Page 45)
    - Lon & Bill on the foot-bridge at Domanine Chandon plant in Napa Valley (Volume 2, Page 46)
    - Bill with his cats, Sabrina & Jasmine - 1986 (Volume 2, Page 47)
    - Lon under 1986 Christmas tree (Volume 2, Page 47)
    - Lon under Christmas tree, 1986 (Volume 2, Page 48)
    - Sabrina loved sleeping under the Christmas tree (1986) and waking to lots of trinkets to paw at, like an infant in a crib with mobiles hanging. (Volume 2, Page 48)
    - Lon in front of 1986 Christmas tree (Volume 2, Page 49)
    - Sunnyvale apartment, `86 (Volume 2, Page 49)
    - Lon & Bill Chistmas day, at the Boardwalk in Santa Cruz 1986 (Volume 2, Page 50)
    - Sabrina & Jasmine at peace (Volume 2, Page 50)
    - Lon gleefully showing the completed autobiographical manuscript, "Spectrum of Life". (Volume 2, Page 51)
    - Lon giving Bill a good morning toast before he goes off to work, 1986 (Volume 2, Page 51)
    - Lon's & Bill's 5th anniversary: 9/13/86 (Volume 2, Page 52)
    - Bill standing at Coit Tower in S. F., Fall of 1986 (Volume 2, Page 52)
    - Lon pondering his 5th year with Bill (Volume 2, Page 53)
    - Bill posing in front of the flower arrangement Lon gave him for their anniversary (Volume 2, Page 53)
    - Bill before anniversay dinner, Sept. 13, 1986 (Volume 2, Page 54)
    - Bill before Anniversary dinner, Sept., 1986 (Volume 2, Page 54)
    - Lon at home, Summer of 1987 (Volume 2, Page 55)
    - Bill and Lon at Coit Tower in S. F., Summer of 1987 (Volume 2, Page 56)
    - Lon and Bill outside Chocolate factory, Summer, 1987 (Volume 2, Page 57)
    - Billy enjoying the S.F. view from Coit Tower, Summer of 1987 (Volume 2, Page 57)
    - Lon and Bill having a picnic in Menlo Park, California in the Summer of 1987 (Volume 2, Page 58)
    - Lon and Bill in S. F., Summer `87 (Volume 2, Page 59)
    - Stockings for Christmas (Volume 2, Page 60)
    - Lon & Bill sharing a loving Christmas Kiss, 1987 (Volume 2, Page 61)
    - Lon & Bill standing in front of our 1987 Christmas tree (Volume 2, Page 62)
    - Lon & Bill knealing in front of 1987 Christmas tree (Volume 2, Page 63)
    - Bill at Shoreline Park in Mountain View, California, Feb., 1988 (Volume 2, Page 64)
    - Sunrise at Shoreline Park (Volume 2, Page 65)
    - Lon at his work place, February, 1988 (Volume 2, Page 66)
    - Bill smirking at Lon, February, 1988 (Volume 2, Page 66)
    - Shoreline Park at dawn (Volume 2, Page 67)
    - Shoreline Park at dawn (Volume 2, Page 68)
    - Bill smiling at Lon, February, 1988 (Volume 2, Page 69)
    - Bill with glasses on, February, 1988 (Volume 2, Page 69)
    - A brisk sunrise before a storm (Volume 2, Page 70)
    - A bright morning before a sunny day (Volume 2, Page 70)
    - It's 5 O'clock ducks - wake up! (Volume 2, Page 71)
    - A string of swans (Volume 2, Page 71)
    - Bill looking for the glimmer of a sunrise through the stormy clouds (Volume 2, Page 72)
    - Rose colored storm clouds (Volume 2, Page 72)
    - Bill at 5 AM without his morning coffee (Volume 2, Page 73)
    - Seagulls floating gracefully in the clouds (Volume 2, Page 73)
    - Ducks heading for shelter from the on-coming storm (Volume 2, Page 74)
    - This walkway is closed to humans, and provides a peaceful shelter to the wildlife (Volume 2, Page 74)
    - These gulls search for a sunny spot in the stormy weather (Volume 2, Page 75)
    - Marshlands bird preserve at dawn (Volume 2, Page 75)
    - The storm had chased away the birds, and I, too, soon left (Volume 2, Page 76)
    - As the clouds thinned this gull soared high above the water (Volume 2, Page 76)
    - If I can only climb a few feet higher each time... (Volume 2, Page 77)
    - Happy Valentine's Day Billy, 1988 (Volume 2, Page 77)
    - Lon & Bill celebrate receiving the bound galleys for Notes On Living Until We Say Goodbye (Volume 2, Page 78)
    - Lon & Bill pose before Lon's first reading & signing for Notes... (Volume 2, Page 79)
    - Bill's Amaryllis (Volume 2, Page 80)
    - Bill ponders the beauty of Nature (Volume 2, Page 81)
    - Bill awakened the morning of his 26th birthday to a decorated house. I had waited for him to fall asleep, then went shopping at all-night markets; it took nearly all night - these are the moments that brought strength to our love in the face of adversity (Volume 2, Page 81)
    - Bill tucks his wallet away as he plans to ride the thriller rides (Volume 2, Page 82)
    - Lon before entering the amusement park where I took Bill for his birthday gift (Volume 2, Page 82)
    - "Which way do I go?" (Volume 2, Page 83)
    - As I said in jest about this photo before Billy would pose for it, "A picture is worth a thousand words" (Volume 2, Page 84)
    - Who would want to??? (Volume 2, Page 84)
    - - Bill comes home from his first hospitalization for PCP; KS biopsy results came back positive on the same day Aug. 25, 1988 (Volume 2, Page 85)
    - - home together at last Aug. 26th (Volume 2, Page 86)
    - The exotic flower arrangement I got for Bill's second coming home after being hospitalized for toxoplasmosis encephilitis - 10/13/1988 (Volume 2, Page 87)
    - Surrounded by life-giving love, Bill finds his reasons to smile (Volume 2, Page 88)
    - A trip to the Pacific coast after Bill's third hospitalization when he could walk along the sea as he resolved that God is values and awe for nature, and that prayer is thought turned to hope. (Oct. 7 - 12) (Volume 2, Page 89)
    - Billy and 1988 X-mas tree (Volume 2, Page 90)
    - 1988 Christmas tree brought to us freshly cut by Robin Amundson and her family (Volume 2, Page 90)
    - Bill - New Years, 1989 (Volume 2, Page 91)
    - Lon - New Years, 1989 (Volume 2, Page 91)
  - Photo Album Five: The Life and Times of Lonnie Gene Nungesser
    - Lonnie Gene Nungesser's birth certificate, born May 30, 1953 shortly after noon. (Volume 5, Page 1)
      (My mom claims that Dad made her finish milking and other chores before he would take her to the doctor, else I would have been born sooner!)
    - Large arrow head for hunting deer, found in the corn fields of our land. (Volume 5, Page 2)
    - The hills that cover our land in the Ozark Mountains - this photo is taken where my ashes are to be spread, for it was one of my favorite places to contemplate life beyond my own. (Volume 5, Page 2)
    - Small arrow head used for hunting squirrels and spearing fish; I found this one near the opening of a natural spring. (Volume 5, Page 2)
    - The quotes were taken with me to recite while watching the sunrise pictured (Volume 5, Page 3)
    - A special sunrise before a storm (Volume 5, Page 4)
    - The beginning part of the path I walked to watch the sun rise (Volume 5, Page 4)
    - Lon at age three (Volume 5, Page 5)
      (Top, center)
    - My sister Mary to my right, and brother Donnie behind us.. (Volume 5)
      (Left)
    - Kansas flat lands behind us, Donnie holding Mary as I sit to the side (Volume 5, Page 4)
      Right,(Right, top)
    - Lon on left, age 2 Mary in center, 3 mths. Donnie on R., at 3 1/2 (Volume 5)
      (Right, bottom)
    - Mary's second birthday Mary on left, Donnie holding the cake for her, and Lonnie showing his disdain for having to face the bright sun (Volume 5, Page 6)
      (Top, left)
    - Lon on left, age 4 Mary Jane on right, age 2 (Volume 5, Page 6)
      (Middle, left)
    - A main street in my home town, Mtn. Grove, Missouri (Volume 5, Page 6)
      (Center, bottom)
    - Fall colors decorate the tree over-hanging Grandma's smoke-house (Volume 5, Page 6)
      (Top, right)
    - The third-generation home in which my father was born and I was reared (Volume 5, Page 6)
      (Middle, right)
    - Neighbor Belle's tree - the change in color warns all that Winter is around the bend. (Volume 5, Page 7)
    - Lonnie at age four (Volume 5, Page 7)
    - One of the quotes that inspired me as a child and still does (Volume 5, Page 7)
    - My Sunday school class - on a poor attendance day! (Volume 5, Page 8)
    - The Pleasant Hill Baptist Church, where I learned & eventually taught. (Volume 5, Page 8)
    - THE LAST SUPPER, a painting I did for my Mom when I was in 6th grade; my parents have recently had it framed, and it now hangs above their kitchen table (Volume 5, Page 9)
    - Certificate of Baptism (Volume 5, Page 9)
    - Certificate of License to Preach the Gospel Ministry (Volume 5, Page 10)
    - High School Senior Photo (Volume 5, Page 11)
    - High School Diploma (Volume 5, Page 11)
    - Lon after Coast Guard Boot camp training (Volume 5, Page 12)
    - The quote that inspired my daily leadership activities (Volume 5, Page 12)
    - Armed Forces I.D. card (Taken after they pulled all 4 wisdom teeth and filled 10 others!) (Volume 5, Page 12)
    - Lon before graduation from the College of Alameda, 1975 (Volume 5, Page 12)
    - Lon on right, seated with his newly elected Coalition student government (Volume 5, Page 12)
      (Bottom, left)
    - Honorable Discharge paper (Volume 5, Page 13)
      (Full page)
    - Lon in "The 01' swimmin' hole" back home, age 22 (Volume 5, Page 14)
    - Lon at age 23 (Volume 5, Page 14)
    - Associate in Arts degree (Volume 5, Page 15)
    - Letter of admission to Stanford University (Volume 5, Page 16)
    - Lon & friends at trail head that leads through Bear Valley to the coast (Volume 5, Page 17)
    - Lon at the Grand Canyon (Volume 5, Page 17)
    - Lon fishing at Yosimite (Volume 5, Page 17)
    - Lon in Stanford class `77 (Volume 5, Page 18)
    - Lon vacationing at Tahoe (Volume 5, Page 18)
    - Lon in "The crystal Cave" (Volume 5, Page 18)
    - Lon's parents, 1972 (Volume 5, Page 19)
    - Dad's parents, 1972 (Volume 5, Page 19)
    - Mom's parents, 1972 (Volume 5, Page 19)
    - Grandpa Nungesser (Volume 5, Page 20)
    - Grandma Nungesser (Volume 5, Page 20)
    - Grandpa tending garden (Volume 5, Page 20)
    - Lon at wedding party, `76 (Volume 5, Page 21)
    - Lon at his wet bar, `77 (Volume 5, Page 21)
    - Lon and sister Mary Jane (Volume 5, Page 21)
      (Bottom, right)
    - Lon as "Rebecca, The Pregnant Pioneer Woman", Halloween, 1977 (Volume 5, Page 22)
    - One of my dinner dates with Advocate owner, David Goodstien, Esquire (Volume 5, Page 22)
    - Sharing Christmas cheer at my home with Dr. Don Clark & family, 1977 (Volume 5)
    - Front page article reporting my activities on "Gay Blue Jeans Day" (Volume 5, Page 23)
    - Expired drivers license (Volume 5, Page 23)
    - Stanford BA degree, with Departmental Honors (Volume 5, Page 24)
    - College Senior photo (Volume 5, Page 25)
    - Lon with Honors advisor, Dr. Philip Zimbardo (Volume 5)
      Bottom, (Bottom, left)
    - The quote that helped me get through Stanford's Honors Program (Volume 5, Page 25)
      Bottom, center)
    - First annual award in honor of Community College founder Leland Medsker, given to a graduate who shows promise as a future University President (Volume 5, Page 26)
    - New York here I am! (Volume 5, Page 27)
    - Stony Brook ID (Volume 5, Page 27)
    - Tracy Kahn, Ph.D. and I acting out an S & M ritual on stage for the Dept. of Psych. (Volume 5, Page 27)
      (Center, left)
    - Tracy, is this an act? (Volume 5, Page 27)
      (Center, right)
    - The final line up, choreographed by Joe, second from left. (Volume 5, Page 27)
    - My first publication (Volume 5, Page 28)
    - Front page article from the Fire Island Villager, June, 1981 (Volume 5, Page 29)
    - Lon sealing his leave of absence from Ph.D. program (Volume 5, Page 30)
    - Lon & Bill go West! (Volume 5, Page 30)
    - Lon in his favorite spiritual place, the Stanford Chapel; quote below helped me fall asleep without anger many nights. (Volume 5, Page 31)
    - Master of Arts Degree (Volume 5, Page 32)
    - My first book! 1983 (Volume 5, Page 33)
    - Press release, 1st book (Volume 5, Page 34-35)
    - Another pool party! (Volume 5, Page 36)
    - A quote that helped me realize the value of a friend (Volume 5, Page 30)
    - Lon in 1983 at Twin Peaks in San Francisco (Volume 5, Page 30)
    - This photo is flanked by quotes at the top and bottom that helped me through the weeks after my AIDS diagnosis. The photo was taken at a special luncheon hosted for Foreign Scholars during the days between my biopsy and diagnosis. (Volume 5, Page 37)
    - Lon one year after diagnosis. (Volume 5, Page 38)
    - Lon & Bill among the flowers that enriched their lives in times of stress, and offered a distraction from tragedy when they needed tending. (Volume 5, Page 39)
    - Another crop of chicks! (Volume 5, Page 39)
    - Lon at the camp fire (Volume 5, Page 40)
    - A sorta-drunk Lon trying to convince Bill we really were not lost! (Volume 5, Page 41)
    - The Gladiolus was bigger than ever this year, and surrounded by Poppies and Bachelor Buttons (Volume 5, Page 42)
    - Lon (1985) on the tractor he learned to drive on (Volume 5, Page 43)
    - News article in local paper, 1985 (Volume 5, Page 44)
    - The Ozark Mountains on our farm in Srping (Volume 5, Page 45)
    - Lon two years after AIDS diagnosis behind the barn built by my Grandfather the year of my father's birth (Volume 5, Page 45)
    - A quote that I tucked in my wallet when I had to go to the doctor or visit a sick friend during the first two years after my AIDS diagnosis (Volume 5, Page 45)
    - My mom, Emma, peering from the milk barn she has spent most of her working life in (Volume 5, Page 46)
    - Mom & Dad (1985) inside the ol' milk barn (Volume 5, Page 47)
    - The Nungesser Family - front row, starting at left: Lonnie, Donnie, and Danny. Back row, starting at left: Brenda Sue, Mary Jane, Linda Lou, Mom & Dad (1985) (Volume 5, Page 48)
    - Lon on left, John David on right. John David was my neighbor and friend as a child. He is married now, and has built the cabin in background with the rocks and trees natural to the Ozarks. A few feet from his front door is a natural spring-fed pond so clear you can see the rainbow stripes on the trout. (Volume 5, Page 49)
    - Grandma Nungesser on far left, Lon in front, Emma in back/center, and Grandma Jarrett on far right - 1985 (Volume 5, Page 50)
    - Grandma Nungesser holding this years prize white Kitten (Volume 5, Page 50)
    - "Planting Seeds of Justice" a poem by Lon G. Nungesser (Volume 5, Page 51)
    - Lon's original greeting card quotes (Volume 5, Page 52)
    - "About the Author" from my second book. (Volume 5, Page 53)
    - Paperback jacket from Epidemic of Courage (Volume 5, Page 54)
    - Cloth jacket from Epidemic of Courage (Volume 5, Page 55)
    - Quotes about Epidemic of Courage (Volume 5, Page 56, 57, 58)
      (Full pages)
    - Another wonderful sunrise (Volume 5, Page 59)
    - The quote that drove me to complete Notes On Living (Volume 5, Page 59)
    - Every sunrise was special, and this one brought out the birds as it peaked over the mountains (Volume 5, Page 59)
    - A self-help brochure I designed for coping effectively (Volume 5, Page 60)
    - Bill was too giggly to give me a Christmas Kiss in 1987 (Volume 5, Page 61)
    - Sandy and Bill under the Christmas tree - she makes him giggle just being in the same room. Only 11 months apart in age, they are as much friends as siblings. (Volume 5, Page 62)
    - Linda Lou gets married, From left: My brother Donnie, his wife; my brother Danny, his wife and one of their kids, Misty, in front; my Father; Linda the beautiful bride, Jim her new husband; my mother holding one of Mary's girls; Mary with another of her girls in front; Bob Rech, Mary's husband; Brenda Sue, Linda's identical twin with another of Mary's girls holding a basket of rose petals; Doug Selby, Brenda's husband. January 2, 1988. (Volume 5, Page 63)
    - Mom at age 53 Dad at age 57 (Volume 5, Page 64)
    - Birds flirting with heaven (Volume 5, Page 65)
    - This pier is a safe place for many Gulls away from gusty winds (Volume 5, Page 65)
    - Clipping of an article entitled, "Shelf Life." (Volume 5, Page 66)
    - Bill at work (Volume 5, Page 67)
    - A representation of how I see Bill when he is playing - soaring high above, free of physical reality (Volume 5, Page 67)
    - I spent 2 hours in thankful prayer at this magnificent sight (Volume 5, Page 68)
    - Bill at Santa Cruz (Volume 5, Page 69)
    - A card from Dr. Zimbardo (Volume 5, Page 70)
    - News release for Notes... (Volume 5, Page 71)
    - News article featuring me (Volume 5, Page 72 & 73)
    - Serene Contemplation (Volume 5, Page 74)
    - Jacket for Notes... (Volume 5, Page 75)
    - Photo & quote are the things that have kept me living with valor and dignity (Volume 5, Page 76)
    - Quotes about Notes... (Volume 5, Page 77 - 79)